WAER Collection
WAER Collection
- Recordings
  - S.U. Wind Ensemble: Part 1, waer_032; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - S.U. Wind Ensemble: Part 2, TAD James, 2/7/65; waer_029; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Senator Goodell Speech at Hendrick’s Chapel on October 14, 1969, waer_095; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
  - Sergio Mendes and Brasil; The Journeymen, waer_117; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
    Mais Que Nada; One Note Samba Spanish Flea; The Joker; Going Out of my Head; Tim Dom Dom; Daytripper; Aqua De Beber; Slow Hot Wind; O Pato; Berimbau; River come Down; Soft Blow the Summer Winds; Black Girl; Dunvya; Fennario; Ride, Ride, Ride; 500 Miles; Rock Me Lord; Make Me a Pallet; Chase the Rising Sun; Cumberland Moutain Deer Chase; Gilgara Mountain
  - Simms Brothers Band, waer_212; Simms Brothers Band recorded by WAER - Syracuse; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - So Jazz Ensemble, waer_070; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
  - Special Address: John Howard Griffin: Part 1, Special Events Department WAER Radio, waer_026; Racial tension problems from racism; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Special Address: John Howard Griffin: Part 2, Hendrick’s Chapel, waer_027; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Special of the Week: Masque of Angels, waer_049; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Sri Shyam Bhatnagar Part 1, waer_178; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - Sri Shyam Bhatnagar Part 2, waer_179; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - Steam Plant show 2 Public Forum, waer_210; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Stewart Brand #1, waer_225; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Stoneground: Set 1 and Set 2a, waer_146; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
  - Stoneground: Set 2, waer_145; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
  - Sunner Sessions Concert, waer_124; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
  - Taj Mahal in Jabberwocky Nov. 9, 1972, waer_078; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
  - Take what you need, it’s yours; People fighting urban renewal, waer_180; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - Tarika Blue #1 music, recorded at studio 3 WAER prefab., waer_055; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
    Povo; Black on Black; Ostinato for Angela; El Hajj; (Untitled); Little Sunflower
  - Tarika Blue #2, waer_056; duplicate of waer_w055?; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
  - The Amazing Stan Lee, waer_196; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - The Feast of Lanterns, waer_248; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - The Financial Plight of the United Nations, waer_150; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
    The DWI and Daniel Webster; Bookmark with Linda Malcom; Sillyness
  - The Hot Dogs, Nov. 11, 1975; waer_115; live broadcast Over WMC - FM from Ardent Studios; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
    Say What you Mean; I Can’t Take Anymore; Thanks; Look at the Sun; When I Come Home Again; Time Is All; Another Smile; I Believe When I Fall for Love It Will Be Forever; Waiting for the Bus; Way to Get to You; Lowdown
  - The Investigation, waer_033; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - The Investigation by Peter Weiss, adapted for broadcast by Ulu Grosbard, waer_034; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - The New Riders of the Purple Sage at Stony Brook, waer_149; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
    Workingman Blues; Watcha Gonna Do; Truck Drivin’ Man; Here Come Trouble; Portland Town; My Sweet Lovin’ One; Dirty Business; Henry; On the Road With You; Louisiana Lady; Honkey-Tonk Women
  - The New Riders of the Purple Sage: Tape 2, waer_136; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
    Brown Eyed Handsome Man; Truck Drivin’ Man; I’m Goin’ On My Way; All I Ever Wanted; Henry; Lool; Women Like a Dollar Bill; The Race is On; Mama Tried; Me and My Uncle
  - The New Riders of the Purple Sage, waer_121; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
    1. Six Days on the Road; 2. I Don’t Know You; 3. Down in the Boondocks; 4. Dirty Business; 5. Sing Me a Rainbow; 6. Garden of Eden; 7. Hello Mary Lou; 8. Henry
  - The Rest of the News, waer_239; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - The River, waer_257; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - The Shirts Live at Jab 9/27/79 Reel 1, waer_242; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - The Shirts Live at Jab 9/27/79 Reel 2, waer_243; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - The Strangers, waer_254; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Theatre of the Air, waer_003; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Theatre of the Air: Bathysphere, waer_005; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Theatre of the Air: Crouse concert, waer_001; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Theatre of the Air: Ghost of Benjamin Sweet, waer_004; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Theatre of the Air: My Client Curley, waer_002; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Theatre of the Air: The Bald Soprano, waer_006; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Theodore H. White Writer Interviewed by VOA, waer_047; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Thirsty Ear, waer_111; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
  - This has been John Brown's Body, waer_054; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
  - Todd Hobin Band - Rock Me To Your Music, waer_228; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Tolley interview, newsmakers special, waer_088; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - Tom Rush and David Bromberg on the S.U. Quad, waer_061; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
  - Tom Rush Concert, waer_099; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
    These Days; Can’t Judge a Book By It’s Cover; Colors of the Sun; Cool Clean Water; Sweet Rotunda; Sweet Baby James; Mint Tulip; Drop Down Mama; No Regrets/ Rockport Sunday; Child’s Song [poor quality]
  - Tom Rush interview + concert, waer_106; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
  - Uncle Vinty #1, waer_065; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
    I Feel So HighI’m In A Frenzy#9What Are You Going To Do About TomorrowLeigh Came the Long Way AroundNo Piano Like this Piano BeforeStory Telling Time (the Owl and the Pussy Cat)Ted and ValerieSo high, So high, So high
  - Uncle Vinty #2, waer_066; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
    1. Gonna Get it on Tonight2. Dixie Melody3. Just a Little Tune About the Moon4. Happy Home (Like the one you have in your eyes)5. Hey Brother Sun (you know I want to be cool)6. Story Telling Time (The Viper)7. The Heckler Song8. The Moon is Never Gonna Get Us Down9. What Are the Chances (when you’re going through changes)10. Mother Nature is Stalling me/Sing This All Together11. What Are You Going To Do About Tomorrow
  - Uncle Vinty: Chris Williamson, waer_071; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
    "1. We’re on to no.92. What are you gonna do about tomorrow3. story time: the own and the pussy4. Animal noises5. Ted and Valerie (sweet mother earth)6. mother nature’s callin me/sing this song all together7. so high so high so high Chris Williamson1. Frontier2. Mr. Frank Jones3. Sometimes it takes a rainy day (waterfall)4. Shine on straight arrow"
  - Underground Music - I’d Rather Die Happy, waer_098; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
  - Unknown, waer_100; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
  - Unknown, waer_103; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
  - Unknown, waer_211; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Utah Phillips - How To Hop A Freight, waer_203; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Voices of the Gods; Julian Jaynes, waer_181; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - WAER production director, waer_089; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - Walking Softly on a Dead Horse, waer_200; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Weather Report: Part 1, waer_109; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
  - Weather Report: Part 2, waer_108; beginning of tape is another band played between set; tape ends in the middle of last tune; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
  - Winning The War: Politics, Myth, and the Reality in the US and S. Vietnam., waer_199; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Winter Consort, waer_116; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
  - WW Today, waer_051; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Youngbloods Interview, waer_107; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
  - [unknown], waer_159; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - [unknown], waer_166; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - [unknown], waer_170; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - [unknown], waer_182; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - [unknown], waer_250; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - [unknown], waer_256; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - [unknown], waer_258; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)